

Skills

- Flutter, Dart, Firebase
- React, Angular
- Javascript, jQuery
- HTML, CSS, PHP
- TypeScript
- Git/Gitlab
- Learning Ability
- Team spirit
- Responsibility and resistance to stress
- Creativity

languages

- Arabic
- French
- English

Interests

- Creative Coding: Exploring personal projects to broaden programming horizons.
- Visual conception:
 Development and modification of user interfaces as well as graphics.
- Volunteering in associations

ABIR CHERIF

Front-end Developer

6

93649677



abir.cherif@ensi-uma.tn



Monastir, Tunisie



https://github.com/abir739



https://www.linkedin.com/in/abir-cherif-931770202/

About Me

Autonomous and enthusiastic, my first experience allowed me to strengthen my skills and grasp various tools and techniques in web and mobile development. Eager for new challenges, I aim to join an organization where I can contribute my dynamism and passion for tackling challenges.

Work Experience

Mobile Developer

07/2023-present

Continuous Net, Sousse, Tunisie

- Design and implementation of front-end features using Flutter and Dart.
- Translation of UX/UI interfaces into tested and optimized Dart code.
- · Creation of reusable widgets and components.
- · Creation of reusable widgets and components.
- Collaboration with the Backend team in an agile SCRUM environment to develop the necessary APIs.

Mobile Development Intern

02/2023-06/2023

Continuous Net, Sousse, Tunisie

- Implementation of a mobile application for managing organized trips, developed using Flutter and Dart.
- The application connects to external APIs to ensure that travel information is updated in real-time.

Web Development Intern

06/2022-08/2022

DRÄXLMAIER Group, Monastir, Tunisie

• Implementation of a web application for electronic document archiving, developed using PHP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, MySQL, Laravel, and Bootstrap.

Web Development Intern

06/2021-08/2021

ENSI, Manouba, Tunisie

 Development of a Web application for skills management of medical staff, using PHP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, MySQL, JQuery, and Bootstrap.

Education

Computer Engineering

National School of Computer Sciences Manouba. Tunisie 2020-2023

2017-2020

Degree in Mathematics and Applications

Higher Institute of Computer Science and Mathematics Monastir, Tunisie